♪♪
That's good.
Real nice, huh?
Drop the knife!
Drop it! Drop it!
- Get back down.
- Easy!
- Put your hands behind your back!
- Okay, okay.
Hands behind your back,
or the next one's going
to be aimed at your head.
Okay, okay.
- Down, down!
- Everybody on the floor.
- Face down!
- Ladies first. That's it, come on.
Come on! What
are you waiting for?
Come on, man! Come
on, fella. Hear me?
Crazy, huh?
Okay, people, Big
Brother's watching.
You move, you bleed.
Ten keys and about
a hundred grand.
We voucher half.
What about Mack
the Knife out there?
He's garbage.
Even if he bothered
to say something,
I'd doubt his own
mother'd listen.
Okay... Ed, Harlan...
All right, you voucher
what's in this bag right here.
Here.
Billy, you take
care of this stuff.
I'll divvy up the cash and
give it to you guys at the Cabin.
Come on, let's get moving.
I haven't had lunch yet.
All right, everybody
up! Time to...
When did this happen?
This morning.
You mean to tell
me you turned in only
half the drugs and money
confiscated during that bust
and kept the rest
for yourselves?
Yes, sir.
And this has happened before?
Yeah, it's a common practice.
"Common practice"?
And until you felt you
should come forward
because you knew the truth
would come out at these hearings,
you were a willing participant
in these illegal
activities, weren't you?
Yes, sir.
Why?
Money.
I'm a cop... who
makes less in a year
than most drug
dealers do in one day.
WRTX News at 4:00
has just learned that
the Burk Commission,
which was formed
last month to investigate
charges of police corruption,
today obtained evidence
that it will present
before the grand jury first
thing tomorrow morning.
Evidence that is expected
to result in the indictment
of several active-duty
police officers.
Members of the commission
refuse to comment on the rumor
that its star witness is an
undercover narcotics agent
who agreed to testify only
after he was promised immunity.
Although... Yeah?
It's not me, Charlie.
I'm supposed to take your
word for that, candy pants?
I'm not a snitch.
Yeah, he was with
me all afternoon.
Besides, the only way to get
hard evidence is with a wire.
They put one on him,
they'd have nothing.
Where were you
this afternoon, Ed?
Oh, I was typing up my report.
No, I-I mean right
after the bust?
We took the
perpetrators downtown,
and you just sort
of disappeared.
- I went to lunch.
- Well, you know,
Harlan and I, we went to lunch.
How come y... how come
you didn't come with us?
I felt like Mexican.
Where?
Some joint near where we were.
Are you gonna... you gonna
come with us to the Cabin?
Charlie, I just don't
feel like it, okay?
Hey, what's the matter?
Don't you want to hang
around with us anymore?
Charlie, um... these things
always make me a little nervous.
Uh, let me be alone
for a while. I'll be fine.
You go to hell, huh?
Say Ed is the snitch and
he testifies, what then?
We get indicted. We go to trial.
Even if they find us not guilty,
we start looking for work.
He testifies, we're dead.
- My nose is clean, remember?
- No, no, no, no, we're dirty,
- you're dirty.
- Ed'll tell them.
Hey, Ed doesn't care who
goes down, long as it's not him.
- Hey, where you going?
- I'm going to call him.
- Forget it.
- No-no-no. No.
Let him go.
Who knows? Maybe lily white
can stop him from testifying.
Commission's still
going to have the tape.
Yeah, it doesn't mean a thing
without collaborative testimony.
Well, boys...
Enjoy.
Money's all there.
Could be it for
a long, long time.
Sweet while it lasted.
What? What's the news?
He said he's gonna talk to me.
I'm gonna go over
his house at 9:00.
That's great.
Fi... uh, finish your
beer. What're you...?
Nah, I-I'm gonna go home.
You know, I want to be
straight when I talk to him.
I'll see you guys later.
Hey, hey-hey... could you
put a good word in for us?
♪♪
Ed?
Hold it right there! Don't move!
It's okay. I'm a police officer.
Well, that makes three of us.
Who had the most shutouts ever?
Walter Johnson, 110.
Give me some hard ones.
All right.
I don't mean throw it hard.
Some hard questions.
Who threw the
most strikeouts ever?
Nolan Ryan, 5,297,
September, '90.
All right, who had the most
runs batted in in a World Series?
Mickey Mantle, 40.
How do you know
all these statistics?
I used to go with a
girl that liked baseball.
Here's a question for you.
Got nothing to
do with statistics.
What was the saddest
day in baseball?
Saddest day in baseball
was the day Babe Ruth died.
No, that was sad.
I mean, it's always sad
when a great one goes, but
what was the saddest day
in the game of baseball?
What was it?
Black Sox scandal of 1919,
when eight Chicago
White Sox players
accepted bribes to
throw the World Series.
Were you involved in that case?
Trying to make me out
to be a hundred years old?
Well, were you?
You know what a little kid
said to Shoeless Joe Jackson
when he came out
of the courthouse?
What'd he say?
He said, "Say it ain't so, Joe."
- Ben.
- Oh, what say, Bob?
- What are you doing out here?
- Hey, Bob.
Well... a cop was
murdered last night.
- Yeah, I...
- Ed Tobias.
Yeah, I read about that.
Another cop was
arrested at the scene.
We got him dead
to rights: motive,
- murder weapon, the works.
- Good.
- Yeah, it is, but,
um...
What's it got to do with me?
Ben, now, this is
a sensitive case.
We got to make sure
Johnny Bauer gets a fair trial.
Now, wait a minute...
Now, this can't look
like a cover-up, Ben.
- No.
- Johnny Bauer needs representation.
He needs representation strong.
Now, Ben, you've got to
do this for the department.
No!
Well, Captain sent me out here.
He knows we've known
each other for years
and have a close
working relationship.
Well, yeah.
Ben, I can't disappoint Captain.
I wish you didn't
know where I live.
Listen, I'll take this, and...
you go change your clothes.
- Bob, let's play catch.
- Hmm?
Let me find out what you know.
Who pitched the most shutouts?
Walter Johnson.
110. Ha!
Baseball's not your
game, is it? All right.
Who pitched the most strikeouts?
Nolan Ryan... 5,297. Ha!
It was my gun,
but I have no idea how
it got into Ed's house.
You keep it at your house?
My locker at the station.
According to the
arresting officer,
you were using your handkerchief
to wipe the prints off of it.
He saw me using my handkerchief
to pick it up off the floor.
And he said that
he and his partner
were dispatched to the scene
as the result of a call to 911.
I don't suppose
you made that call.
I-I was going to call for help,
but I never got the chance.
What were you doing
over there, anyway?
I went over there to talk to Ed.
- What about?
- About what he was gonna say to that
grand jury.
I wanted to make
sure he told the truth.
Which was what?
That I was clean.
According to what I
hear, your undercover unit
falsified vouchers
and kept confiscated
drugs and money
as a matter of course.
I was never part of it.
You knew about it.
When I found out, I
said, "No, thank you,"
and I immediately
put in for a transfer.
Transfer, hell. Why
didn't you tell somebody?
Because you don't do that.
Not if you're a cop.
Not when your life could damn
well depend on the willingness
of another guy to
stick his neck out.
You turn your
back, you walk away.
But above all, you don't snitch.
Garbage!
You tell the truth.
You yell your head
off. You find a way.
I don't want to take this case.
I'll do the best I can.
You may not have killed
Ed Tobias, I hope not,
but you've got to
know one thing.
You'll never be a cop again.
Maybe you're not too
old to learn another trade.
Well...
Who knew you were going
over to his house that night?
Charlie Orbach, Billy Pierce
and Harlan Fondy... my partners.
Your partners?
Hmm.
Now, the body was found
in the chair over there.
Your client was found right
here with the murder weapon.
Hmm. Did you find the
bullets that were fired?
No, just the one the coroner
dug out of Tobias's left ventricle.
The next-door neighbor
said he heard two shots.
What happened to the other one?
Well, we couldn't
find a trace of it.
But the guy had on his TV.
No telling what he really heard.
Was Mrs. Tobias here last night?
Ed sent her and
the kid off to a movie.
Huh.
You know, Bob, this
case isn't nailed down
near as tight as you say.
Considering what Ed Tobias
was going to say
to that grand jury,
there are three other men
who had motive to kill him,
and you don't have any
witnesses or fingerprints
or powder burns
or... Oh, almost forgot.
Tobias always kept
a gun... right here.
Loaded.
Clean. Within easy reach of
anybody sitting at this desk.
Now, if somebody unexpected
showed up here last night,
what's the first thing Tobias...
A cop... would've done?
Go for his gun.
Now, the drawer was unlocked.
He could've got
his gun. He didn't.
Why? Because the
guy that killed him
was the guy he was
expecting: Johnny Bauer.
Well, well...
Hey, what's with
you and the door?
- Hmm?
- You're making me nervous.
I'm taking Eileen to lunch.
She's meeting me here.
That's the second
time this week.
Well, nothing wrong
with paying attention
to your wife, is there?
Excuse me,
gentlemen. I-I... I...
I'm Ben Matlock. I
represent Johnny Bauer.
The waitress over there
told me you're his... partners.
Yeah, I'm Charlie
Orbach. How're you doing?
This is Billy Pierce over here.
Harlan Fondy.
Have a seat. Buy you a drink.
No.
So, how's Johnny boy doing?
How would you think?
Must be tough for him in jail.
How's the case going?
Well, you can look
at it a couple of ways.
Either Johnny
killed Ed Tobias...
Which I doubt, 'cause
he had no motive...
Or someone else did it who
knew he was going over there.
And that would be one of you.
Ed was our partner and friend.
Ed Tobias was about to snitch.
If he had corroborated
what was on that tape
before the grand jury, you'd
all be in the Atlanta Penitentiary.
We were all here that night
from the time we got
off duty till around 10:00.
- Just ask the waitress.
- I did.
She said you all
came in about 5:30,
but she couldn't say
what time you left.
Well, you know,
you're just gonna have
to take our word for it.
You know I won't do that.
Harlan?
Ready to go?
My wife and I have
lunch reservations.
You didn't have any more
questions, did you, Mr. Matlock?
Well, just one more thing.
Hon, meet me by the door.
If Johnny did
this, they'll get him.
Otherwise, they'll
get one of you.
And one thing I'm sure of,
you'll all go to
prison for dealing.
And when you get out...
And I hope it's a long time...
Not only will you
never be cops again,
but other cops will be
looking over your shoulders
the rest of your lives.
May I have your ticket, sir?
Well, my car is
right over there.
Why don't I just go get in it?
I have to have your
ticket, sir, and three dollars.
Three dollars?!
I wasn't in there three minutes.
Those are the rules, sir.
Not a penny till
you bring me my car
and there better
not be a mark on it.
Thanks a lot.
How long do you
keep those tickets?
60 days, in case anybody tries
to claim we damaged his car.
Is the license plate
number on there, too?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah?
Thanks.
Thank you.
The change is, uh, what? $2.50?
Hey, how you guys doing?
Mr. Matlock.
Ah, Detective Pierce, hello.
Is this your car?
As a matter of fact, it is.
Actually, I... I knew that.
I checked all the
parking tickets
they collected at Captain's
Cabin the night of the murder.
All three of you were
there, but it seems that
one of you left at, uh,
8:30 and never came back.
Is that right?
Where'd you go, Detective?
None of your damn business.
That what you're
going to say in court?
You don't have an
alibi, and I can prove it.
Might as well tell
me the truth now,
'cause sooner or later you're
going to have to face the music.
Just because Pierce left the bar
before the murder was committed,
- doesn't mean he did it.
- That's right.
In fact, the only thing we
know is that his car left the bar.
Anybody could've done it.
That's right, too.
Not so hard.
You think you're Nolan Ryan?
Sorry. What's your next move?
Well...
Ow!
Since Mr. Pierce thinks I
know something already,
I thought I'd ask you to
go over to the bar and...
Do a little eavesdropping?
- Yeah.
- Right now?
Yeah.
- -All right.
- Wait!
Uh, yeah, Ben Matlock.
Who is this?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay. I'll be there.
Who was that?
Sounded like one of our boys.
What'd he want?
Said he had some information
for me on Ed Tobias's murder.
Told me to meet him at the back
of the Summit Street
Bakery in 20 minutes.
- I'll go with you.
- No, I'll be all right.
- You go on over to the bar.
- After I go with you.
Okay, you drive.
Why do you want me to drive?
'Cause my hand's sore, Nolan.
Okay, let's see the cash.
- Excuse me?
- Hey...
you don't get the stuff until
we see the cash, all right?
Now, come on. Let's go.
Uh, I-I think you must
have us confused with
somebody else. I...
What is your problem?
Huh? Quit jerking us
around and get out the cash.
He's talking to a
gray-haired guy in a gray suit.
Tip they gave us was
right on the money.
Let's take them now.
Police! Everybody freeze!
That's Ben Matlock! Hold it!
You're surrounded!
Get your hands in the air!
Get down, Mr. Matlock!
All right, don't shoot!
Don't shoot! I give up!
I give up, man!
Get down on the ground!
Get down!
- All right! All right!
- Yeah!
- Down on the ground!
- Take it easy, man!
Damn you, Conrad.
I was safe.
But you weren't satisfied.
I had to be filthy, too.
Damn.
Why aren't you filthy?
I fell in the bread.
It's right across
Peach Tree Street...
Excuse me. Can I just
borrow that for a second?
Thank you.
What happened to you?
I walked into a little shootout
between some drug
dealers and the SWAT team.
Thought you boys might
like to be in on the fun.
Whoa, can't believe that.
New look for you, guys!
Chan? Pierce.
I'll meet you at 8:00. Be there.
♪♪
Hey, Billy.
Morning, Bob.
Hey, I need to talk to
you. You got a second?
Sure.
Uh, not out here, though.
Uh, come on.
Have a seat, Billy.
What's going on?
Well, Mr. Chan here
says you were with him
the night Ed Tobias
was murdered.
Were you?
Yeah.
Why'd you tell me
that you were with your
friends at that bar all night?
Because Bobby here is one
of my informants, all right?
I met with him so he
could give me the name
of a couple new players.
I didn't tell you about it,
because if words gets
out he's on the payroll,
he's dead meat. Okay?
Everybody happy now?
Good.
Mr. Chan's not your
snitch, Billy; he's your buyer.
He buys the stuff you don't
voucher when you make a bust.
Hey, look, I don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
Hey, tell them.
Tell them how
you're my informant.
It's all right.
You shouldn't have
beat on me like that, man.
I don't like that,
you understand?
I told them the truth.
He's lying.
- I don't think so.
- Hey...
Look, believe whatever
you want to believe.
Either way, I got
an airtight alibi
for the time of the murder.
Mr. Chan says you sold
him confiscated drugs, Billy.
He's ready to
testify to that effect.
What you've got is a problem.
Hey, what jury
is going to believe
street trash like that?
He's your alibi.
You better hope some jury
somewhere believes him.
He's my informant.
Matlock's paid him to say all
those other things about me.
He's trying to make Johnny Bauer
look good by making me look bad.
Don't you see that?
You're in trouble, Billy.
You need help.
Coincidentally, so
does Mr. Matlock here.
Who knows? If
everybody's amenable,
uh, maybe we could...
work something out.
What? A deal?
Call it a mutual...
back-scratching arrangement.
Let's hear it.
Uh... H... Hi, Eileen.
Uh, is Harlan here?
Sure, come on in.
Thanks.
Hey, Billy, what's up?
Hey, man. How're you doing?
Uh, w-we need to
talk, man, privately.
No problem. I'll go for a walk.
No, no, no, you don't have to.
Uh, just wait in the other room.
No, I'd rather go for a walk.
All right, listen, uh,
go towards the park
and I'll catch up to you.
- See you, Billy.
- See you later.
Hey, couldn't
you've just called?
This lawyer, Matlock,
he keeps hassling me
about where I was
the night of the murder.
He's even got Bob
Brooks in on the act.
Oh, so you're
thinking of confessing?
I didn't do it.
Who did or didn't do it
was something we
agreed not to discuss.
- Remember?
- Yeah. Yeah, but I didn't know
I was gonna be the only one
to wind up taking
any heat on this thing.
Now, I want to know
what happened that night.
Go ask Orbach.
Come on, Harlan!
Now, I got a right to know
who I'm sticking my neck
- out for, don't I?
- Billy, what I'm saying is
I was at the Captain's
Cabin till 10:00.
If you want to know what
happened, go ask Charlie.
You mean, he
left before you did?
He left right after you,
sometime between
8:30 and quarter to 9:00.
You know where he went?
I don't know. He said he
had something about a date.
Look, Billy, I'm sorry, okay?
I have problems
of my own, all right?
Me and Eileen are
not getting along.
You sorry piece of slime.
What was your
relationship to the
deceased, uh, Ed Tobias?
He was my partner.
And your undercover unit would
feign interest in, uh,
buying drugs and then
arrest the traffickers when
they tried to sell them to you.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
And isn't it true
that you routinely
kept part of the drugs
and money you confiscated
during these arrests?
No, it is not.
And isn't it true that Ed Tobias
was about to give testimony to
that effect before a grand jury?
Not to my knowledge.
Isn't it true that
he was murdered
to keep him from exposing
your unit's illegal activities?
If you want to know
why he was murdered,
try asking your client.
Move to strike.
Nonresponsive.
Witness's last
remark will be stricken.
All right, Detective,
where were you
between 8:30 and 9:30...
the night your partner
was murdered?
I was at the Captain's
Cabin bar with Harlan Fondy.
Uh-huh. And how far is
that from Ed Tobias's house,
you know?
I don't know. I have no idea.
Four-tenths of a mile.
I clocked it twice...
Walking distance.
Which explains why you
left your car at the bar.
You left shortly
after 8:30 and walked
to Ed Tobias's house
and shot him, didn't you?
I repeat...
I was with Harlan Fondy that
night at the Captain's Cabin
from 5:30 until almost 10:00.
If I told you that I
have an eyewitness
who said you left between
8:30 and a quarter to 9:00,
would that refresh
your recollection any?
Who?
Harlan Fondy.
Now, I'm gonna play a
tape-recorded conversation
between two of your partners...
I'm sure you'll
recognize their voices...
And you tell me if it refreshes
your memory suddenly.
Now, I want to know
what happened that night.
Go ask Orbach.
Come on, Harlan! I got a right
to know who I'm sticking
my neck out for, don't I?
Look, Billy, what I'm saying is,
I was at the Cabin
till 10:00 that night.
You want to know what
happened, you got to go ask Charlie.
You mean he left before you did?
He left right after you,
between 8:30 and
quarter to 9:00.
You still say you were at
the bar all night, Mr. Orbach?
All right, all right,
I left just like he said
around quarter of 9:00.
I had a date.
You had a date?
Did she mind
walking? I mean, your...
your car was at the bar.
She picked me up.
- She picked you up?
- Yeah.
She picked... me up.
Ah. Oh.
Well, where'd you go?
Oh, about five blocks away.
Empty parking lot.
Stayed there for about
an hour, and, uh...
you know... talked.
Oh, yeah. Does she have a name?
Yeah, she has a name.
It's Eileen Fondy.
You were with
your partner's wife?!
I didn't want to
say anything before,
you know, out of
respect for his feelings.
But I... I changed my mind.
No further questions.
Are you going to
subpoena Eileen Fondy?
No.
I think Charlie
Orbach's telling the truth.
Well, if she's Charlie's alibi,
and Bobby Chan is Billy's alibi,
it's got to be
Harlan Fondy, right?
Yeah.
Keep away from her,
Charlie! Hey, Charlie!
- You keep away from...!
- Hey! Hey!
- Knock it off!
- Oh, don't be such an idiot!
Take it easy.
D-D-Did you see that?
See what?
His-his arm's bleeding.
Uh, Ms. Tobias, uh, I'm Ben
Matlock, Johnny Bauer's lawyer.
You were at the funeral parlor
the last time I was over here,
and I-I couldn't give sympathy
for myself and for Johnny
for you and your son.
What do you want?
Well, I was hoping I could
come in and I-look around again.
Okay.
The police were here for
two whole days, Mr. Matlock.
I really don't know
what you expect to find.
Well, the truth be told,
I don't know myself.
Um, I understand you
went to the movies that night.
Yes. Ed called me in here
right after he talked to Johnny,
and, uh, asked me to take
Randy... that's our son...
And leave the house for a while.
Yeah. Did he do that often?
- Sometimes.
- Hmm.
He worked undercover,
so I just figured that
came with the territory.
Uh-huh, yeah, yeah.
Did he... did he tell
you anything else?
No.
But I should have known
something was going to happen,
because when I came in
here, he was checking his gun.
Uh, I see. He-He...
He-He... kept
his gun, I believe,
in this top drawer, didn't he?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
I remember because
Randy took it to the shooting
range a few days earlier,
and he put it back
without cleaning it.
Ed was furious.
He made him promise to
clean it the very next morning,
or he wouldn't be able
to use the car for a month.
You mean the gun was dirty
when he put it in the drawer?
Yes. Even I was upset
with him about that.
Hmm.
It's clean as a whistle now.
That's not possible.
Maybe your son kept
his promise, after all.
My son hasn't been near this
desk since the night Ed died.
He can hardly go
into the kitchen.
Did you tell the police that?
No.
I... I-I guess I was too upset.
Wonder how this gun got cleaned.
Uh, Detective Fondy,
would you please tell the
court who Red Huntsinger is?
He's an ex-cop who hangs
out at the Captain's Cabin.
Shoots a mean game of pool.
Aha. You ever
play pool with him?
Sure, all the time.
He says you played pool with
him the night of the murder,
- is that right?
- Yep.
- Says he beat you.
- Usually does.
He said you put a dollar
down on the table for a rematch,
but, uh, by the time it came
your turn to play him again,
you were nowhere to
be seen. Where'd you go?
Bathroom, probably.
I don't know.
He said you were gone
a good half hour, and...
and when he finally
did see you again,
you had hurt your
arm or something
and couldn't play anymore.
What happened to
your arm that night?
Bumped my elbow.
I don't remember.
Yeah. Is it better now?
Oh, yeah, I heal quickly.
Yeah, I'll bet you do... big,
strong fella like yourself.
I hear you jog.
- Yeah, about four times a week.
- Yeah.
Uh, how long's it
take you to jog a mile?
About eight and a
half minutes or so.
You could easily, then,
jog four-tenths of a mile
in, uh, under five
minutes, couldn't you?
Couldn't you?
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah. Half hour'd be
more than enough time
to jog over to Ed Tobias's
house, shoot him with the gun
you'd taken earlier from
Johnny Bauer's locker
and jog back, wouldn't it?
I never left the bar that night.
That's just what
your partner said.
You sure you're not lying, too?
I was at the bar
from 5:30 till 10:00,
and you can't prove otherwise.
I'm afraid I can, Detective.
I'm showing you a revolver.
I ask that it be marked
Defense Exhibit "G."
And the prosecutor here
has already stipulated
that this is the revolver
that was found in Ed Tobias's
desk the night he was killed.
You recognize this
pistol, don't you?
No.
It was in the upper
right-hand drawer, remember?
He took it out when you walked
into the room instead of Johnny.
- I wasn't there that night.
- He knew instantly
his life was in danger.
He took the gun
out in self-defense.
He shot you just a second
before you shot him.
Only his bullet
went into your arm,
and yours went into his heart.
- That's not true.
- That explains why
the neighbor heard two shots.
Only one slug was ever found.
The other left with you,
because it was in your arm,
- wasn't it?
- No.
And you stayed and cleaned
this gun and put it back
in the drawer, so that no
one would ever suspect
it had been fired
and start wondering why
Johnny wasn't walking around
with a bullet in
him, didn't you?
- I wasn't there that night.
- You killed
Ed Tobias to keep
him from exposing you
as a crooked cop, didn't you?
No. No, no, no, none
of it's true, none of it.
Then show us.
What?
Your arm.
Your left arm that
started bleeding
during the scuffle out
in the corridor yesterday.
I tripped while I was
jogging a couple of days ago.
I scraped it up pretty badly.
That's why I was bleeding.
There's a big difference
between a scrape
and an almost-healed
bullet wound.
I'm sure we'll be able
to tell that difference.
- Just show it to us.
- Look, look...
ask my wife.
Wouldn't she know
if I'd gotten shot?
She'd know your
arm was bandaged.
She wouldn't necessarily
know why, unless you told her.
Just show it to us.
Or shall I call...
Dr. Richmond to the stand?
It was fairly simple to
track down the doctor
who dug that bullet
out of your arm.
All your friends
know Dr. Richmond.
I can call him, but...
it'd save us a lot of
time if you'd just show us.
I don't have to show
you a damn thing.
Okay.
No, you don't.
Dr. Richmond will testify,
and the fine police of
Atlanta will investigate,
and that'll be it.
All I really have to do today
is to show reasonable doubt
that my client
committed this crime,
and I believe I've done that.
One-one more... one more thing.
After the Atlanta
Police Department
finishes its investigation,
I'm sure they'll find
what we all suspect... that there
was a great deal of hanky-panky
going on with illegal money
and cocaine by Mr. Orbach,
Mr. Tobias, Mr. Pierce
and of course, Mr. Fondy.
And they'll pay
the price for that.
As for my client,
he killed no one.
He made a mistake...
A kind of big one.
He put his trust
in the wrong place.
Whatever happens,
when it's finally
over for him, I
hope he's learned,
and can once
again live in society
as a happy and fully honest man.
Thank you.
What you got?
- That's a curve, baby, curve.
- Yeah.
- Curve.
- Get it here.
Get it in, get it in.
- Oh!
- Talk to me.
- Hey.
- What?
Hey, look.
Hi.
Want to play?
- Yeah, sure. -Yeah.
- Yeah. -Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Yeah, put the girl up.
I hope you... I'm giving... I'm
giving you everything I've got.
Hey, batter, hey,
batter, hey, batter.
Come on there!
www.tvsubtitles.net